{"data":[{"question":"Each of the boy ________ won a prize.","a":"have","b":"has","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present Perfect: \n+ Express action happened at an unspecified time before now. The exact time is not important.\u00a0\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs. Do not be misled by what follows of.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"He's got a lot of books ________.","a":"read","b":"to read","c":"reading","d":"for read","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Have\/get sth to do sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"I heard the door ________.","a":"open","b":"to open","c":"opening","d":"a & c are correct","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Find\/ see\/ watch\/hear...+ Verb (with to) :you find \/see or watch the whole action.\u00a0\n- Find\/ see\/ watch\/hear...+ Verb_ing : you find \/see or watch part of the action.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"In your office, who is responsible for ________ the mail?","a":"take care of","b":"caring of","c":"taking of","d":"taking care of","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Be responsible for doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"There is ________ to believe that he is not prepared for his future work.","a":"reason","b":"reasonable","c":"reasonably","d":"a reason","answer":"4","explain":"\n- There is + singular noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"This company offers a lot of ________ jobs.","a":"attractive","b":"attracted","c":"attraction","d":"attract","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Adj + Noun: adj often used to modify noun.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"The farmers need ________ their crops.","a":"rotate","b":"to rotate","c":"rotating","d":"a & b are correct","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Need + To be Past Participle\/ V_ing: if before \"need\" is not person.\u00a0\n- Need + To Verb: If before \"need\" is person.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"A new road is being ________ in my village.","a":"build","b":"built","c":"to build","d":"building","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present continuous + passive voice: be + being + PP.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"When the wastes are poured into the atmosphere, the air ________ unpleasant to breathe.","a":"become","b":"becomes","c":"became","d":"has become","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Future tense\/simple present tense + while\/when + simple present tense.\u00a0\n- Subject (the air) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"},{"question":"Now farmers are accustomed ________ this fertilizer to their fields.","a":"apply","b":"applying","c":"to apply","d":"to applying","answer":"4","explain":"\n- To be accustomed to doing something: to be familiar with something and accept it as normal.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"28","type":"1"}]}